<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Maker Arts</title><link>https://makerarts.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Maker Arts</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 22:13:44 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://makerarts.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Science Awards</title><link>https://makerarts.github.io/scienceawards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 21:59:31 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://makerarts.github.io/scienceawards/</guid><description>CREST is the British Science Association&amp;rsquo;s scheme for STEM project work that inspires young people to think and behave like scientists and engineers. We offer the bronze and silver awards:
Bronze An introduction to STEM project work for 11+ year olds working individually or in teams.
Typical age: 11+
Time to complete: 10 hours
Silver A challenge for 14+ year-old students to run their own STEM projects in teams or individually</description></item><item><title>Arts Awards</title><link>https://makerarts.github.io/artsawards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 21:02:09 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://makerarts.github.io/artsawards/</guid><description>We run science and arts awards programs for home education and other groups.
Arts Awards We offer three arts awards from Trinity College London. Arts Award inspires young people to grow their arts and leadership talents: it&amp;rsquo;s creative, valuable and accessible.
Discover The discover award is an introductory award from Trinity College London aimed at young people under 25. We host the entire program with students building up an arts log with:</description></item><item><title>Employability</title><link>https://makerarts.github.io/employability/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 21:01:59 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://makerarts.github.io/employability/</guid><description>A large part of our mandate is to inspire and assist young people with the skills and confidence required for a career in art, science, technology. engineering and maths.
We provide half-day, weekly and flexible midterm programmes and can work with parents or educational insitutions to cater for all time constraints.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://makerarts.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 21:36:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://makerarts.github.io/contact/</guid><description>Send an email to Sue sue@makerarts.co.uk or Abi abi@makerarts.co.uk.
You can find us at
Maker Arts CIC, Suites B &amp;amp; C, 1 Parkside Road, Paignton TQ46AE
Our front door&amp;rsquo;s what3words is ///shield.cakes.closet</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://makerarts.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 21:28:29 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://makerarts.github.io/about/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re a Torbay based Community Interest Company set up to support young people who may be facing personal challenges attending mainstream education. Young people can take part in creative workshops, learn new skills, build on their confidence and discover employment opportunities in the art and STEM sectors that they may never have thought about. We use an holistic approach to help young people feel supported, gain knowledge and break down barriers that may be contributing to their disengagement from education.</description></item></channel></rss>